Guide to the Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records, ca. 1960-1989
Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records,
- Series I. Assignments
  - September 1979
    - Fuertes Paintings in Olin (R) for Chronicle, 790914 (Box 16)
    - Harold Uris Testimonial Dinner, NYC (S), 790915 (Box 16)
    - Crickets (R) for Chronicle, 790916 (Box 16)
    - William Keeton and Steven Emlen for Newsweek (R), 790917 (Box 16)
    - Architecture School Reunion, 790918 (Box 16)
    - Doris Robinson Shell House Dedication, 790919 (Box 16)
    - Football, Colgate, 790920 (Box 16)
  - October 1979
    - Handicapped Bus, United Way w/Earl Brown (R), 791001 (Box 16)
    - Arnot Forest (R) Chron., 791002 (Box 16)
    - Employee Day:, 791003 (Box 16)
    - Bar-B-Que at Barton Hall (S), " (Box 16)
    - Bar-B-Q and Football (Cornell vs Bucknell), " (Box 16)
    - Football, " (Box 16)
    - Football game and Biug Red Band, " (Box 16)
    - 150 lb. Football (A), " (Box 16)
    - Trustee Council Weekend (S), 791004 (Box 16)
    - Breakfast, " (Box 16)
    - Discussion Groups, " (Box 16)
    - Donlon Display Case Dedication, " (Box 16)
    - Football, Cornell vs Harvard, 791005 (Box 16)
    - " (Box 16)
    - Neal R. Stamp (R) Chron., 791006 (Box 16)
    - Baker Institute,(R), 791007 (Box 16)
    - Odd Fellows (Chron.), " (Box 16)
    - [none], 791008 (Box 16)
    - Women's Crew at Doris Robison Shell House (S), 791009 (Box 16)
    - ROTC Display Case (R), 791010 (Box 16)
    - President Rhodes' Birthday Party (R), 791011 (Box 16)
    - VIP's at Johnson Museum (R) Color, 791012* (Box 16)
  - November 1979
    - Sina-Than (Chron.), 791101 (Box 16)
    - Ellis Robison w/Memorabilia for Schoellkopf Display Case (R), " (Box 16)
    - ROTC Display Case Dedication (R), 791102 (Box 16)
    - Bob Purcell and Guests for Homecoming Game (R), 791103 (Box 16)
    - Hillel Anniversary (S), 791104 (Box 16)
    - 39 & '49 Class Reunion (S), 791105 (Box 16)
    - Homecoming Game Half Time (copy neg.) (S), 791106 (Box 16)
    - Campus Scenes (R), 791107 (Box 16)
    - Martha Van Rensselaer Interiors (R), 791108 (Box 16)
    - David Rockefeller for B & PA (S), 791109 (Box 16)
    - Alva Taylor for Kodak (R), 791110 (Box 16)
    - Ugly Man on Campus (C), 791111 (Box 16)
    - Special Project: Arts and Sciences Professors for Newsletter (R), 791112 (Box 16)
    - Jon Clardy, " (Box 16)
    - Peter Gierasch, " (Box 16)
    - Frank Drake, " (Box 16)
    - David Usher, " (Box 16)
    - Sherman Cochran & Martie Young, " (Box 16)
    - Pamela Parker, " (Box 16)
    - Nathaniel Owings w/Architecture Students (R), 791113 (Box 16)
    - Hockey Line - Tickets (R), 791114 (Box 16)
    - COSEP Reception w/President Rhodes (S), 791115 (Box 16)
    - Jim Maas - Drunken Driving Film (R), 791116 (Box 16)
    - "Nice Day" (R), 791117 (Box 16)
    - "Rainy Day" (R), 791118 (Box 16)
    - Dining in: Dining Halls & College Town (R), 791119 (Box 16)
    - N. Campus, " (Box 16)
    - Campus Scenes (C), 791120 (Box 16)
    - COSEP (S), 791121 (Box 16)
    - Baldwin at Africana 10th Anniversary, " (Box 16)
    - Demonstration, Iran vs US (R), 791122 (Box 16)
  - December 1979
    - Women's Sports - Ice Hockey (Cornell vs Cortland) and Fencing (R), 791201 (Box 16)
    - Campus Scenes at Noon Hour (R), 791202 (Box 16)
    - Symphonic Band Concert in Willard Straight Hall (R), 791203 (Box 16)
    - Gingerbread House built by two students from Hotel Ezra Cornell, in the Statler (R) (Chron.), 791204 (Box 16)
    - Fraternity Life, Dinner with Guests, Pi Kappa Alpha (R), 791205 (Box 16)
    - Hockey, Cornell vs New Hampshire (A), 791206 (Box 16)
    - Sage Chapel Christmas Concert with Choir (R), 791207 (Box 16)
    - Books Written by Cornell Authors, in the Sibley Library (R), 791208 (Box 16)
    - Students Studying in the Andrew D. White Reading Room of Uris Library and in Olin Library (R), 791209 (Box 16)
    - Snow Scenes, " (Box 16)
    - Final Examinations in Barton Hall (R), 791210 (Box 16)
    - Sale of the Odd Fellows Home to Cornell University School of Hotel Administration (R), 791211 (Box 16)
  - January 1980
    - Lloyd E. Carter-Leavitt, Development Officer, Arts & Sciences (S), 800101 (Box 16)
    - Registration in Barton Hall (R), 800102 (Box 16)
    - Women's Basketball, Cornell vs C.W. Post (S), 800103 (Box 16)
    - B & PA Art Gallery Opening (R), 800104 (Box 16)
    - Student Activities Fair at Willard Straight, 800105 (Box 16)
    - " (Box 16)
    - Campus Scenes, Store, WSH, Olin Lib., & Dog (R), 800106 (Box 16)
    - C.A.C.O. Meeting in New York, Bob Smith, 800107 (Box 16)
    - Computer Graphics, Architects, Campus Scenes (C), 800108 (Box 16)
    - Barton and Teagle Afternoon Jocks (R), " (Box 16)
    - George Hildebrandt, Economics & I & LR (S), 800109 (Box 16)
    - Director of Center for Study of American Political Economics, " (Box 16)
    - I & LR Interiors (S), 800110 (Box 16)
    - Dorothea DeHart, Lady Vet Student, National 4-H Award Winner,(R) and Temple of Zeus for Poetry Reading, 800111 (Box 16)
  - February 1980
    - Athletics: (S) Cornell vs. Yale Wrestling, 800201 (Box 16)
    - " Cornell vs. East Stroudsburg, women's Gymnastics, " (Box 16)
    - " Cornell vs Penn, Men's Gymnastics, " (Box 16)
    - " Cornell vs Yale, Basketball, " (Box 16)
    - "Cornell vs Yale, Basketball, " (Box 16)
    - " Cornell vs Harvard, Hockey, " (Box 16)
    - Heptagonals, " (Box 16)
    - New Construction Site for Biological Science (R, C), 800202 (Box 16)
    - Richard Strassberg, Labor Documentation Center, ILR (R), 800203 (Box 16)
    - B & PA, Tom Calo and Deaf Student, Steven Luscinski (R), 800204 (Box 16)
    - Liberty Hyde Bailey Hortorium (R), 800205 (Box 16)
    - Dale Rosenthal for Ben DeWinter (R), 800206 (Box 16)
    - Society for Creative Anachronism (R), 800207 (Box 16)
    - Center for International Studies, continuing, (S), 800208 (Box 16)
    - " Icelandic Books, Olin Library, " (Box 16)
    - " O'Connor, " (Box 16)
    - " Esman, " (Box 16)
    - " Sisler, " (Box 16)
    - " [Guesler] ?, " (Box 16)
    - " Styer, " (Box 16)
    - " [Landman] ?, " (Box 16)
    - " Gil Levine, " (Box 16)
    - " [illegible] ?, " (Box 16)
    - Guide Dogs and Campus Scenes (R, C), 800209 (Box 16)
    - Air Sampler at Uris Library, Campus Scenes (R, C), 800210 (Box 16)
    - B & P A, Tire Sale Promotion (R), 800211 (Box 16)
    - Snow Scenes (R), 800212 (Box 16)
    - Tom Miller, New Basketball Coach (R), 800213 (Box 16)
    - Peter Kuniholm, Classics, Tree Ring Dating; Spacecraft Planetary Imaging Facility, Space Science (R, C), 800214 (Box 16)
    - Chaim Potok at Hollis Auditorium (R), 800215 (Box 16)
    - Veterinary Medicine: Dean Edward C. Melby, Jr., Associate Dean Charles G. Rickard, Professor Emeritus Elis P. Leonard (R), 800216 (Box 16)
    - TV in Uris Library Listening Room (R), 800217 (Box 16)
    - Prince Norodom Sihanouk at Cornell, 800218 (Box 16)
    - Snow Scenes and Experimental Shots (R), 800219 (Box 16)
    - Ted Lowi, Government (S), 800220 (Box 16)
    - B & P A, Former Secretary of the Navy, J. William Middendorf (R), 800221 (Box 16)
    - President Rhodes at Mary Donlon Hall, with Students (R), 800222 (Box 16)
    - Gift to Wason Collection at Olin Library from Prince Sihanouk (R), 800223 (Box 16)
    - Copy Negative for Harry Caplan's Postcard (in w/color negs), 800224 (Box 16)
    - Copy Negative of falcons from color slide, 800225 (Box 16)
  - March 1980
    - Check Passing for Development; Pot Shop Scenes (R), 800301 (Box 16)
    - David W. Corson and the History of Science Exhibit at Olin Library (R), 800302 (Box 16)
    - Members of the Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra conduct a Master Class in Barnes Hall (R), 800303 (Box 16)
    - Emily Metcalf w/Anne Martindale Williams, Cellist, PSO, " (Box 16)
    - Sheila Kilcoyne " " " ", " (Box 16)
    - Sheila Kilcoyne " " " ", " (Box 16)
    - Sally Gross " " " ", " (Box 16)
    - Elizabeth Blaeuer " " " ", " (Box 16)
    - Lois Darlington " " " ", " (Box 16)
    - Sophia Pao " " " ", " (Box 16)
    - Diane Cifonelli w/ Bernard Goldberg, Flutist, PSO, " (Box 16)
    - Diane Cifonelli w/ Bernard Goldberg, Flutist, PSO, " (Box 16)
    - Liisa Ambegaokar w/" " " ", " (Box 16)
    - Pittsburg Symphony Orchestra Concert (S), 800304 (Box 16)
    - "Grand Duke" by the Cornell Savoyards (S), 800305 (Box 16)
    - Green Dragon Parade, 800306 (Box 16)
    - Open Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 800307 (Box 16)
    - Model and Paper Airplane Contest at Barton Hall (R), 800308 (Box 16)
    - Green House Energy Saver (R), 800309 (Box 16)
    - President Frank Rhodes at Spacecraft Planetary Imaging Facility Dedication (R), 800310 (Box 16)
    - Professors: George Gibian, Russian Lit.; Leonard H. Babby, Linguistics; Alexamder Zholkovsky, Russia (R), 800311 (Box 16)
    - Architect's Model of New Biological Sciences Building (R), 800312 (Box 16)
    - Campus Scenes in Snow (C), 800313 (Box 16)
    - C.E.S.R. Dedication- Synchrotron (R), 800314 (Box 16)
    - Cameo Collection in Olin Library (R), 800315 (Box 16)
    - Chemistry Professors: Wiesenfeld, Ganem, Porter, Morrison, McMurray (R), 800316 (Box 16)
    - Ag Day at Willard Straight Hall (C), 800317 (Box 16)
  - April 1980
    - Jordani Scoiety, Pre-Auction (R), (Chron.), 800401 (Box 16)
    - FALCON Students to Japan, (R), 800402 (Box 16)
    - Firewheel Project (R) (Chron), 800403 (Box 16)
    - Campus Scenes (R), 800404 (Box 16)
    - B & P A Art Gallery Opening #2, (R), 800405 (Box 16)
    - Golden Phone Award (R), 800406 (Box 16)
    - Open House at the School of Veterinary Medicine (S), 800407 (Box 16)
    - Bloodmobile and Energy Conservation at WSH (R), 800408 (Box 16)
    - Anabel and Myron Taylor Copy Negatives, 800409 (Box 16)
    - Earth Rise and Campus Tours (R), 800410 (Box 16)
    - Hong Kong Night at WSH (S), 800411 (Box 16)
    - Engineering Egg Drop (R) (S), 800412 (Box 16)
    - Professor Joseph Thomas for B & PA (R), 800413 (Box 16)
    - "Anything that Floats (But a Boat)" Race, Fuertes Exhibit in Olin (R), A00414 (Box 16)
    - Phi Psi 500 Race (S), A00415 (Box 16)
    - Health Awareness Day, Karate, Gammelan (R), A00416 (Box 16)
    - Willard Straight Craft Fair, A00417 (Box 16)
  - May 1980
    - Springfest, 1980, A00501 (Box 16)
    - Risley Fair, Electric Car (R), A00502 (Box 16)
    - Blossom time (tech. Pan in Levy formula) (R), A00503 (Box 16)
    - Amino Acid Analysis, Curtis Fullmer, Director; Vet College Wild Bird Project, Douglas McCoy, Director (R) Chron., A00504 (Box 16)
    - B & P A Art Gallery Opening, Peter Kahn Exhibit (R), A00505 (Box 16)
    - Outstanding Seniors (R) Chron., A00506 (Box 16)
    - Jason Seley at the Foundry, new Dean of Art, Architecture and Planning, (R) Chron., A00507 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1980, A00508 (Box 16)
    - James A. Friend Family Distinguished Professor Award (R & S), A00509 (Box 16)
    - Herb Finch at Icelandic Collection, Olin Library (R) Chron., A00510 (Box 16)
  - June 1980
    - Peony Society with Marjorie Cornell, at Plantations (R), A00601 (Box 16)
    - Cool Greenhouse Dedication, at Plantations (R), A00602 (Box 16)
    - Chinese Word Processor and Group for China Tour (S), A00603 (Box 16)
    - Alumni Reunion: Million Dollar Classes (R & S), A00604 (Box 16)
      - Dean Gift & Library Associates Dinner (S) (Box 16)
      - Continuous Reunion, Athletics (S) (Box 16)
      - Milton S. Gould, '30, Rhodes & Crampton (S) (Box 16)
      - Statler Meeting, Stewart, Uris, Gould, Winnert (R) (Box 16)
      - Rhodes Alumni Report, Uris, Barton (R) (Box 16)
      - Barton (R) (Box 16)
      - Barton (S) (Box 16)
      - Uris Garden Dedication (R) (Box 16)
      - Plantations, Treman Concert (S) (Box 16)
      - Giving Club Reception, Sibley Library (R) (Box 16)
      - Gould, Lattomus, General Scenes (R) (Box 16)
      - Football Alumni, Lattomus '55 (S) (Box 16)
      - Oarsmen, Boathouse (S) (Box 16)
      - Canoeing, Beebe, Scenic, Alumni (S) (Box 16)
      - Athletic, Superstars, Egg Toss, Solar (S) (Box 16)
      - Kids, Fire Engines, Golf, Alumni, Schoellkopf (S) (Box 16)
      - Reunion Dinner '50, Hoy Field (S) (Box 16)
      - Reunion Dinner '50, Hoy Field Bar-B-Q '55 (S) (Box 16)
      - Alumni, Band, Hoy Field Bar-B-Q '55 (S) (Box 16)
      - Tents at Mary Donlon (S) (Box 16)
    - Rare Book Donations for Ellis Robison (R), A00605 (Box 16)
    - Connie Cook Retirement (C), A00606 (Box 16)
    - Professor Robert Richardson, Low Temp. Physics Lab w/helium (R), A00607 (Box 16)
    - Album Produced by Kel Arden & Publications (R), A00608 (Box 16)
  - July 1980
    - B & P A executive Development Summer Session (R), A00701 (Box 17)
    - Eleanor Rice, University Registrar (R), A00702 (Box 17)
    - Chinese Visitors to Cornell: Wason Collection, Woolworths (R), A00703 (Box 17)
      - Goldwin Smith, Cullen House (S) (Box 17)
      - Johnson Museum (R) (Box 17)
      - Language Lab, Morrill Hall, Word Processor (S) (Box 17)
    - Miriam Hutchins, Judicial Administrator (R), A00704 (Box 17)
    - Computer terminal with Doug Gale (R), A00705 (Box 17)
    - Synchrotron, new CLEO (R), A00706 (Box 17)
    - James A Baker Institute (R), A00707 (Box 17)
    - Jason Seley and CAU classes at the Foundry (S), A00708 (Box 17)
    - C.U. VIP's Trip to China, by John McCoy, A00709 (Box 17)
    - Parks, Summer Fun, Campus Scenes (S), A00710 (Box 17)
    - Keith Kennedy in Japan, by K. Kennedy, A00711 (Box 17)
  - August 1980
    - Architecture Students, Fossils, A00801 (Box 17)
    - Freshmen Again: Arrival (R), A00802 (Box 17)
      - President's Convocation (R) (Box 17)
      - Freshmen Olympics (R) (Box 17)
      - Bar-B-Q, Rug Sale at WSH (S) (Box 17)
      - Bar-B-Q,Career Center, Plant Sale, Ag Quad (R)) (Box 17)
      - Water Fight in the Dust Bowl (S) (Box 17)
      - Registration (R) (Box 17)
      - Temple of Zeus, Orientation (S) (Box 17)
      - Volleyball, Campus scenes, Fun in the Sun (S) (Box 17)
      - Registration (S) (Box 17)
      - North Campus, Hasbrouck, Campus scenes (S) (Box 17)
      - Big Red Band, Fun in the Sun (S) (Box 17)
      - Registration, Chinese (S) (Box 17)
    - Construction Scenes (R), A00803 (Box 17)
    - Test Roll, Technical Pan in Rodinal (R), A00804 (Box 17)
    - Test Roll, (S), A00805 (Box 17)
  - September 1980
    - Chinese Visitors, A.D.White Locker Key, (R), A00901 (Box 17)
    - Workers at Gannett Health Center, Crowds at Campus Store, A00902 (Box 17)
    - Quad Scenes (w/clouds), North Campus, Dorms at Donlon, A00903 (Box 17)
    - Ag Quad Scenes, Mann Library, etc. (good shots of students), A00904 (Box 17)
    - Minority Students w/Rhodes and Trustees, A00905 (Box 17)
    - Craft Fair, Physics Class (R), A00906 (Box 17)
    - Student Closeups, Campus Scenes, Art Class Outdoors, etc., A00907 (Box 17)
    - Thomas Gold, Astro Physicist, (Chron.) (R), A00908 (Box 17)
    - Gannett Health Center Dedication, A00909 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes, Views from Hollister Roof (for Gannett), A00910 (Box 17)
    - George Heekin, P.R. Shooting around campus, Rhodes and Football team, A00911 (Box 17)
    - Lester B. Knight, P.R. Shooting, Chicago Dinner, A00912 (Box 17)
    - Scholarship Students (Mrs. Barr), A00913 (Box 17)
    - Football, Cornell vs Princeton, A00914 (Box 17)
    - Law-grad Setup, Gannett follow up, A00915 (Box 17)
    - Copy Negative from 35mm slide for University Publications, A00916 (Box 17)
    - Black Studies Conference, I & L R School, A00917 (Box 17)
  - October 1980
    - Gannett Health Center, Follow ups, Interiors, A01001 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes, Noyes Center, Dining, W. Campus, etc., A01002 (Box 17)
    - Large Viewing Video Screen, Uris Library; Reading Rooms, (Chron), A01003 (Box 17)
    - Employee Day, A01004 (Box 17)
    - Football; Rutgers, A01005 (Box 17)
      - Brown (Box 17)
      - Penn (Box 17)
    - Book Bears Sale, A01006 (Box 17)
    - Albert Dorskins, Donation of Ansel Adams Photographs to Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art, A01007 (Box 17)
    - Copy Negatives of Photographs from China (4), A01008 (Box 17)
    - Profs. Bondi, Salpeter, Gold, Terzian (Space Science), A01009 (Box 17)
    - Professor William F. White, I L R (Chron.), A01010 (Box 17)
    - Another (God Help Us) Computer, New DEC 1060 (Chron.), A01011 (Box 17)
    - Plantations Luncheon at Robison Hall of Fame, A01012 (Box 17)
    - Trustee Council Weekend '80, A01013 (Box 17)
    - Art, Architecture and Planning, area photographs, Franklin, Sibley, etc., A01014 (Box 17)
    - United Fund, Ziegler, McNair, Pai, Rhodes, (Chron.), A01015 (Box 17)
    - Fall Campusscenes, A01016 (Box 17)
    - Icelandic Ambassador and reception at Olin Library, (Chron.), A01017 (Box 17)
    - President Rhodes presents Film Awards to Sen. Wm. Smith, (Chron.), A01018 (Box 17)
    - Homecoming Groups, A01019 (Box 17)
    - Test Roll, Benson uses Idiot Camera, A01020 (Box 17)
    - Color Aerials and Campus Scenes, A01021 (Box 17)
  - November 1980
    - The "Robey" Committee - Rare Book donations, A01101 (Box 17)
    - Charles Rehmus, ILR School Dean, with Primitive Masks, A01102 (Box 17)
    - Dr. Jacobson, Plant Growth Chambers in Boyce Thompson, (Chron.), A01103 (Box 17)
    - Newly Renovated Upson Hall Student Lounge, (Devel.), A01104 (Box 17)
    - Robert Smithson Exhibit at Johnson Museum, (Reports), A01105 (Box 17)
    - Floyd Newman 90th Birthday Party, A01106 (Box 17)
    - Upson Hall Lounge with VIP's, Salvation Army Food Campaign at Campus Store, A01107 (Box 17)
    - Nice Snow Scenes, A01108 (Box 17)
    - Harold Scheraga, Chemistry Department, A01109 (Box 17)
  - December 1980
    - Biological Sciences and Submicron Construction Up-date, A01201 (Box 17)
    - Dale Corson and Richard Phelan, with Corson Sundial on engineering Quad, A01202 (Box 17)
    - Professors Richardson and Lee with Laboratory set-up. (Chron), A01203 (Box 17)
    - Dean Beck's Last Class for Hotel School, A01204 (Box 17)
    - Memorial Service for Harry Caplan, at Sage, A01205 (Box 17)
    - School of Hotel Administration, A01206 (Box 17)
    - Virginia Rinker, Personnel Development, (Chron.), A01207 (Box 17)
    - James A. Baker Institute, A01208 (Box 17)
  - January 1981
    - Temple of Zeus-Lydia, A10101 (Box 17)
    - U.S. News & World Reports: Silbey, Polenberg, Lynn (negatives sent to U.S. News & World Reports), A10102 (Box 17)
    - James A. Baker Institite, A10103 (Box 17)
    - School of Veterinary Medicine, A10104 (Box 17)
    - Tennis "Bubble"; I.D.Cards at Stone Palace; Engineering Reception for New Students at Olin Hall, A10105 (Box 17)
    - Dr. Szalay, Boyce Thompson Institute (Chron.); Engineering Reception for New Students at Olin Hall, A10107 (Box 17)
    - Registration, A10108 (Box 17)
    - Dean of Students Drinkwater at Johnson Museum, " (Box 17)
    - President's Reception, " (Box 17)
    - Registration, " (Box 17)
    - Kiplinger Luncheon: class of '81 Challenge gift, A10109 (Box 17)
    - Richard Horodek (Development), A10110 (Box 17)
    - Snow Scenes, A10111 (Box 17)
  - February 1981
    - Hockey, Cornell vs Princeton, A10201 (Box 17)
    - Nanette Fondas, Rhodes Scholar (Chron), A10202 (Box 17)
    - William Bassett in CHESS Lab, (Chron) and Plantations Snow Scenes, A10203 (Box 17)
    - James Scannell, Dean of Admissions, A10204 (Box 17)
    - Student Composers Rehersal, A10205 (Box 17)
    - Wrestling, Cornell vs U. of Penn., R 1 & R 2, A10206 (Box 17)
    - Womens' Hockey, A10207 (Box 17)
    - Law School, Interiors and Exteriors, A10208 (Box 17)
    - Theatre Arts: Acting II w/Prof. Steve Cole, A10209 (Box 17)
    - ": Intermediate Dance w/Prof. Peter Saul, " (Box 17)
    - ": Costume Design, " (Box 17)
    - ": Advanced Dance, Costume Design, " (Box 17)
    - ": Lighting Design, " (Box 17)
    - ": Stage Combat, Mark Boyan, " (Box 17)
    - Presentation; Empire State Masonry Assoc., of slides to School of Art, Architecture and Planning, A10210 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes, (Chron), A10211 (Box 17)
    - School of Veterinary Medicine, A10212 (Box 17)
    - Amade Trio Rehersal, A10213 (Box 17)
    - Sports:, A10214 (Box 17)
  - March 1981
    - Robison Dedication at Lynah Rink, A10301 (Box 17)
    - Taming of the Shrew Rehersal, Theatre Arts, A10302 (Box 17)
    - Shirts Off - Student Demonstration - Tuition Hike, (Chron.), A10303 (Box 17)
    - Richard Kuslan, Ham Radio Writer, (Chron), A10304 (Box 17)
    - Business Executives Forum at B & P A School, A10305 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes, A10306 (Box 17)
    - Golden Phone Award, George Morrison and Moon Rock, (Chron.), A10307 (Box 17)
    - Grace Kobayashi, Architect Award Winner, (Chron), A10308 (Box 17)
    - Green Dragon Parade, A10309 (Box 17)
    - Marshall Scholarship Winners, (Chron.), A10310 (Box 17)
    - Untitled, A10311 (Box 17)
    - Ag Day at Willard Straight, A10312 (Box 17)
    - Jack Lewis Retirement Party, A10313 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes with 300mm and 20mm lens, A10314 (Box 17)
    - Frank Vertucci and Acid Rain Tests, (Chron.), A10315 (Box 17)
    - Board of Trustees, Open Meeting at Statler Aud., A10316 (Box 17)
    - Women's Varsity Lacrosse, A10317 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes, A10318 (Box 17)
    - Blue Heron Aerial Survey, (Chron.), A10319 (Box 17)
  - April 1981
    - The Great Chicken-on-the-Egg Photo; Banner for Painting Exhibit at Johnson Museum, A10401 (Box 17)
    - Early Spring Campus Scenes, A10402 (Box 17)
    - Rhodes Presents Color Aerial to Mayor Bordoni, Outdoor Classes, Malcolm Bilson with new Piano, (Chron.), A10403 (Box 17)
    - Early Spring; Latin American Day at WSH, Minorities, (Chron.), A10405 (Box 17)
    - Model Airplane Contest in Barton, ASME, (Chron.), A10406 (Box 17)
    - Uris Library Addition Ground Breaking, A10407 (Box 17)
    - Campus Scenes, A10408 (Box 17)
    - Arthur Dean Book Awards to Students, (Chron.), A10409 (Box 17)
    - Profesor Charles Van Loan and computers (Repts), A10410 (Box 17)
    - Diagnostic Lab, Vet School, (Sol), A10411 (Box 17)
    - Engineering Egg Drop, ASME, (Chron.), A10412 (Box 17)
    - Health Day; Hotel Ezra Cornell, A10413 (Box 17)
  - May 1981
    - Engineering Students Construction at Treman Park, A10501 (Box 17)
    - Lacrosse, Cornell vs, A10502 (Box 17)
    - Spring hits the Campus, A10503 (Box 17)
    - Phi Psi 500/Gamelan, A10504 (Box 17)
    - Sir Robert Cotton, of Australia with President Rhodes, A10505 (Box 17)
    - Arlene Alde speaks to Jim Maas' Psychology Class, A10506 (Box 17)
    - Lacrosse, Cornell vs Penn., A10507 (Box 17)
    - High and Wide angles, Campus scenes, A10508 (Box 17)
    - Last Day of Class/Springfest, A10509 (Box 17)
    - Carl A. Kroch Visits Cornell, Endowed Chair, University Libraries:, A10510 (Box 17)
    - Airport Arrival, " (Box 17)
    - Campus Walk to L. Martin's Office, " (Box 17)
    - L. Martin's Office/Rare Book Room, " (Box 17)
    - Rare Book Room, " (Box 17)
    - Luncheon and Reception, " (Box 17)
    - Luncheon and Reception, " (Box 17)
    - Luncheon, " (Box 17)
    - Luncheon/History of Science Exhibit at Olin Libe., " (Box 17)
    - Campus Tour, " (Box 17)
    - President's Office, " (Box 17)
    - President Rhodes with Outstanding Seniors, A10511 (Box 17)
  - June 1981
    - Trustees' Meeting, A10601 (Box 17)
    - Commencement 1981, A10602 (Box 17)
    - Hydroplant- Equipment Lift, A10702 (Box 17)
    - Plantation Dedications:, A10703 (Box 17)
    - Heasley Dedication, " (Box 17)
    - Heasley Dedication/Young Dedication, " (Box 17)
    - Young Dedication, " (Box 17)
    - Young Dedication, " (Box 17)
    - Deans Garden Dedication, " (Box 17)
    - Deans Garden Dedication, " (Box 17)
    - Deans Garden Dedication, " (Box 17)
    - Tjaden Hall Dedication, A10604 (Box 17)
    - Arthur Dean Visit, A10605 (Box 17)
    - Alumni Reunion 1981, Barton Hall, A10606 (Box 17)
    - Aaron L. Binenkorb Center Dedication, A10607 (Box 17)